Contact

(617) 383-3745 (Mobile) jgwalsh@bu.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/jgregorywalsh (LinkedIn)

siena-csm.symplicity.com/profiles/ jgregorywalsh (Personal)

Top Skills

Analytical Skills Client Services Project Planning

J. Gregory Walsh

Mental Health Counselor

Albany, New York, United States

Summary

Experienced Counselor working closely with providers to gather accurate, clinically relevant information. Works well with diverse client populations in one-on-one and group settings. Offering research experience along with comprehensive knowledge of statistics, data collection, and data analysis.

Experience

McLean Hospital Mental Health Counselor May 2014 - September 2018 (4 years 5 months) Brighton, Massachusetts

McLean-Franciscan Child and Adolescent Inpatient Program

Morgan Stanley Internship May 2011 - August 2011 (4 months) Albany, New York Area

Education

Siena College BA, Psychology · (2009 - 2013)

Boston University
Graduate Studies, Clinical Psychology · (2014 - 2019)